堕胎等于谋杀
堕胎伤害女性
丢   人
通 奸 者
删除瑞秋?
删除
追踪
道格拉斯·斯坦普
删除联系人瑞秋
手机追踪
中断
菲茨
副总统刚刚走进司法部大楼
The Vice President just entered the Department of Justice.
现场请到的是艾拉·萨伊德
We're here with Ayla Sayyad,
她发表在《华尔街电讯报》上的文章
whose Wall Street Telegraph article
直接促成了这次调查  艾拉
catalyzed the investigation. Ayla.
关键问题在于白宫与此事是否有牵连
The issue at stake is whether the White House was in any way involved.
是否有国外资金用于换取政治支持
Was foreign money traded for political favors?
又是否对外交关系产生影响
Did it influence diplomatic relations?
单是为来自中国的政治献金洗白就是违法的
Just the act of laundering Chinese contributions is illegal.
如果这笔钱对白宫决策产生影响的话
If it had a significant impact on White House policy,
那就是更严重的罪行了
that's a far more serious crime.
你曾多次与丹尼尔·拉尼根会面
You've met with Daniel Lanagin on multiple occasions.
没错  2003年起我们曾11次共处一室
We were in the same room, yes, on 11 occasions since 2003.
但其中我们交谈过的只有三次
But we only spoke on three of those occasions.
那几次已经标出来了
Those instances are highlighted.
你们谈了什么
What did you discuss?
那都是在筹款会上
Well, these were fundraisers.
我对着几十号人发表讲话
I speak to dozens of people,
也没有什么特定的话题
usually about nothing at all.
我是南方人  邓巴女士
I'm southern, Ms. Dunbar.
我妈妈教导我
My mother taught me that
席间讲话不仅礼貌
conversation during mealtime is not only polite,
还有助消化
it aids the digestive process.
那你没有跟他谈到过
So you didn't speak to him
阿道希部落向这些超级政治行动委员会捐款的事吗
about the Adohi tribe's contributions to any of these super PACs?
绝对没有
Absolutely not.
我从不和支持者提超级政治行动委员会
I never discuss super PACs with any supporters.
我们熟悉法律规定
We both know the law.
在这些礼节性的谈话中
During one of these polite conversations,
拉尼根先生可曾向你提起过冯山德
do you recall Mr. Lanagin ever mentioning Xander Feng?
我想没有
I do not.
你听说过这个名字吗
Does that name mean anything to you?
你是说除了铺天盖地的媒体报道吗
Other than being plastered all over the news?
从这个角度说  就像我也听说过金·卡戴珊
In that regard it means as much as Kim Kardashian.
那我再说得明确些
Then let me be more specific.
你对冯先生的政治活动有什么了解
What knowledge do you have of Mr. Feng's political activities?
这是你丈夫的意思还是
Is this coming from your husband, or is it...?
是我的意思
From me.
而且不是说我不再支持法案了
And it's not that I don't support the bill anymore.
只是采访的事
It's just the article.
我们已经答应让马特做专访了
We've promised Matt an interview.
那往后推几周吧
Maybe in a few weeks,
等调查尘埃落定之后再说
once the investigation has died down.
《纽约时代杂志》可不会干等着我们
The New York Times isn't going to wait for us.
他们已经腾出十月份的封面
They've already scheduled the cover for October.
鉴于我们的安排
Based on our timing --
那就恕难参与了
Then I can't be a part of it.
是因为嘉乐威的事  是不是
It's the Galloway nonsense, isn't it?
克莱尔  别这么说
Claire, come on.
没事的
It's okay.
你直说就行  我们是朋友
You can say so. We're friends.
的确影响不好
It doesn't help.
你不会真相信我
You don't actually believe I --
当然不信
No.
但国内还是有不少人信的
But enough of the country still does.
加勒特现在需要争取每一份支持
And Garrett needs every bit of support he can get right now.
那你心意已决了
So there's no convincing you?
我会尽可能帮你
I'll help as much as I can.
悄悄地帮
Quietly.
有传言说你和冯先生
There are rumors that you and Mr. Feng
在去年五月的贸易峰会上进行了私下接触
served as back channels to the trade summit last May.
没错  就是"传言"
Exactly. Rumors.
峰会期间冯就在美国境内
We have Feng in the U.S. during the summit.
就算他做了私下接触
Well, if he was back-channeling,
就算我知情
and even if I were aware,
这种外交接触一般都是保密的
any form of diplomatic communication is usually classified.
你和总统说起过冯吗
Have you ever discussed Feng with the President?
北京每一个权势人物我们都会说起
Any major player in Beijing is worthy of discussion.
那就是承认了
So that's a yes.
只是陈述一般情况
It's a general comment.
你在能源危机期间与别人说起过他吗
Did you discuss him during the energy crisis?
我猜你是指跟他合资投资精炼厂的
I assuming you're alluding to the refinery co-venture with --
没错  我是指雷蒙德·塔斯克
Yes. With Raymond Tusk.
我们从来没聊起过精炼厂
The refinery was never part of our conversation.
我们要的是能立即见效的方案
We needed an immediate solution.
建精炼厂在短期内什么都解决不了
A refinery would have solved nothing in the short term.
而且据我所知  这交易最后黄了
And it's my understanding that deal fell through.
没错  但塔斯克拿到了补贴
Correct. But Tusk did receive a subsidy.
其他核电供应商也都拿到了
As did every other nuclear energy provider.
但他和冯有联系
But his connection with Feng,
还有钐补贴
then a subsidy on samarium --
没人从这笔补贴中获利
Nobody made any profits off these subsidies.
至多也就是保本而已
At best they were breaking even.
事实上  雷蒙德一开始还反对补贴的事
In fact, Raymond fought us on the issue.
那我们再说说杰斐逊港大桥吧
Then let's back up to the Port Jefferson Bridge.
这也怨不得她  这的确值得担忧
I don't blame her. It's a valid concern.
告诉他我不会谈嘉乐威的事
Tell him I won't engage on Galloway,
所以干脆也别问
so there's no point in asking.
这可是马特·贝
This is Matt Bai.
他要问什么我们说了不算  而他肯定会问这个
We can't dictate what he'll ask. And he will ask.
那我就说我不会回应这些无聊八卦
Well, then I'll just say I won't answer tabloid questions.
这是个合理的问题
It's a legitimate question.
丑闻对选举有什么影响
How the scandal could affect the vote.
我建议我们也不做了
Look, I say you pull out, too.
取消掉整篇专题
We scrap the whole piece.
杰姬在和我们对着干
Jackie is fighting us.
总统方面又指望不上
The leadership is noncommittal.
我们需要这篇专访让大家重新关注法案
We need this article to refocus attention.
但这于你不利啊
But it'll hurt you.
对你的形象和法案都不利
Both your personal image and the bill.
但如果我们谁都不靠
But if we cut the cord,
约好的两场采访
we schedule two interviews,
就这么取消了  马特不会生气吗
then we cancel, won't Matt be furious?
那么大家只会看到我们的退缩
The story will be about pulling out.
我们要权衡利弊
We're talking about the lesser of two evils.
我不希望你成为目标
I don't want you to become the target,
-使我们的努力白费  -如果不是我去呢
- to undo all the work - Then what if it's not me at all?
可你说第一夫人不打算
But you said the first lady wasn't going --
不是她  是其他人
Not her. Someone else.
建设大桥是否是换取切断共和党资助金的筹码
Was the bridge a trade-off to prevent additional GOP funding?
据我所知
As far as I know,
这座大桥是总统在兑现
the bridge was a delivery on a promise
他对选民做出的承诺
the president had made to the voters.
还没问完吗
Are we finished here?
快了
Almost.
你会见过多少位国会议员  邓巴女士
How many members of Congress have you interviewed, Ms. Dunbar?
200吗
About 200?
194位
194.
我想帮忙
Well, I want to be of help,
但我想前面194位都已经说得差不多了
but I doubt I can offer any more than the 194 that preceded me.
我得到了一些有用的证词
I have gotten some useful testimony.
-从谁那儿  -众议院高层
- From who? - A high-ranking House member.
领导层的吗
In the leadership?
我不能说
I'm not at liberty to say.
鲍勃·博奇  杰姬·夏普
Bob Birch? Jackie Sharp?
这个人说他参加了7月14日
This individual says he attended a meeting
在总统办公室的会议
July 14th in the Oval Office.
她说是个男的  那么一定是博奇
She said "He," so it must have been Birch.
雷蒙德肯定能轻易收买他
I'm sure Raymond had no trouble buying him off.
你也参加了那次会议
You attended that meeting also.
看来是这样的
It appears so.
你还记得那次会议的主题吗
Do you recall the subject of that meeting?
一波共和党的攻击广告
A wave of conservative attack ads.
我们没有足够财力与之抗衡
We were being outspent.
你一定很震惊吧
It must have been quite a shock
拉尼根转而把钱捐给了另一党派
when Lanagin's tribe shifted contributions to the other party,
之前他们从没给共和党捐过钱
when they hadn't given a single dime to the Republicans before that.
这的确会令我们震惊
Well, it would have been a shock,
但我们当时并不知道钱是哪来的
but we didn't know where the money was coming from at the time.
据我的线人说
According to my source...
鲍勃·博奇
Bob Birch.
我的线人说  当时预计有两千五百万
My source says the estimate was 25 million.
引用你说的话
You said, and I quote,
"凭空出现这么多钱
"With this kind of influx,
肯定有人违规了"
you can be sure somebody isn't playing by the rules."
像是我说过的话
Sounds like something I might say.
鲍勃的记性比我好
Bob has a better memory than me.
杰斐逊港大桥刚获批
The money stopped just after
这笔钱就中断了
the Port Jefferson Bridge was approved.
你是真有想法
Is there a theory here,
还是查不出头绪就瞎猜
or are you just grasping at straws?
大桥与冯有关
The bridge leads to Feng.
冯与拉尼根和塔斯克有关
Feng gives me Lanagin and Tusk.
塔斯克和总统
Tusk and the president --
邓巴女士  你想玩六度分隔的话
Ms. Dunbar, you want to play six degrees of separation,
还能扯上吉米·霍法和教皇
you could throw in Jimmy Hoffa and the pope.
82年神秘失踪的工会领袖
那么一度分隔如何
Then how about one degree of separation?
道格拉斯·斯坦普  你的幕僚长
Douglas Stamper, your chief of staff.
这是7月14日他在拉尼根的赌场
This is him at Lanagin's casino July 14th.
我用这些申请了搜查证  调出了飞行记录
I used these to get a warrant for flight records.
第二天  斯坦普先生飞去北京
The next day, Mr. Stamper was on a flight to Beijing.
他为什么去赌场
Why was he at the casino?
为什么去北京
And why was he in Beijing?
我想与委托人谈谈
I would like to speak to my client.
请吧
Please.
我很努力
I work hard.
我不拖泥带水  我知道重要的是什么
I keep things simple. I know what my priorities are.
但是有这么个人
But there's this -- this person.
她不在我的生活中  而是在我生活的边缘
She's not even in my life, except on the edges,
所以界限很模糊
making things blurrier.
这并不让我想喝酒
It doesn't tempt me to drink.
那感觉更像...
It's more like she --
她给我的感觉就像我喝酒时的感觉
it's more like she feels what it was like when I was drinking.
总是无法满足
When I couldn't get enough.
不管我喝多少酒
No matter how many drinks I had,
总是喝不够
I wanted another.
我不想和她在一起
I -- I don't want to be with her.
我是说  我想
I mean, I -- I -- I do.
但是
But
她更像是我女儿
it's more like she's my daughter.
或者我母亲
Or my mother.
我也不知道了  太乱了
I don't know. This is fucked up.
慢慢说
Take your time.
我不该再跟她联系了
I should cut her off.
就像戒酒一样
The way I did with booze.
就这些  说完了
That's all. I'm done.
谢谢你与我们分享
Thanks for sharing.
我们需要一些时间回答你的问题
We'll need some time before responding to your questions.
我愿意等
I could wait as long as necessary.
可能要花上一段时间
It could take a while.
事关国家安全
There are national security matters at stake.
副总统需要咨询顾问
The vice president needs to consult with his advisors.
国家安全
National security?
你真要用这招吗  奥利弗
Are you really gonna play that card, Oliver?
他的回答可能涉及保密信息
His answers could entail classified material.
我们什么时候能得到回应
When can we expect a response?
我会通知你的
I'll let you know.
我们可以拿走这些截屏照片吗
May we hold onto the screen cap?
请便
Be my guest.
我们会尽快联系你  邓巴女士
We'll be in touch soon, Ms. Dunbar.
副总统先生
Mr. Vice President?
不要认为你这就没事了
If you think you're insulated, don't.
我们调查的不止道格拉斯·斯坦普
Our investigation is much bigger than Douglas Stamper.
就到这儿吧  邓巴女士
That's enough, Ms. Dunbar.
多谢你的配合  副总统先生
Thank you for your time, Mr. Vice President.
乐意合作
Happy to cooperate.
刚出虎口  又入狼窝
From the lion's den to a pack of wolves.
如果你是滴血的肉  那就杀了别人
When you're fresh meat, kill,
给他们更新鲜的肉
and throw them something fresher.
你好  我是菲茨
Hey, I'm Fitz.
道格
Doug.
你要知道  你可以自己硬挺着
Yeah, you know, uh, you can isolate,
独自承担这一切
white-knuckle this shit if you want.
或者你也可以向他人求助
Or you can ask for help.
你有担保人吗
Got a sponsor?
不用  都已经14年了  我没事
No. It's been 14 years. I'm good.
电话在背面  如果你改主意的话
Number's on the back, if you change your mind.
我以为你有司机
Thought you had a driver.
我有
I do.
我不希望他听到什么
I didn't want him overhearing anything.
你根本就不该来这个州
You shouldn't even be near this state.
我不在这儿
I'm not really here.
去加州绕了点远路
Long layover on my way to California.
稽核员
I've got auditors,
和联邦探员都在我办公室
federal agents in my office,
查看每一份文件和档案
going through every file, every document.
他们连我的垃圾都翻
They're going through my god damn trash.
如果她传唤你就坚持保持沉默
Just stick to the Fifth if she subpoenas you.
他们怎么知道去查斯坦普
Well, how do they know to look for Stamper?
专查那天的录像
To search the tapes on that exact day?
别乱下结论
Don't jump to conclusions.
你这是要牺牲我
You're throwing me under the bus.
安德伍德才是对头  你不是
Underwood's the roadkill. Not you.
他们要坑我
They're going to fuck me.
他们会找到办法
They'll find a way.
-而且你也知情  -如果是那样
- And you know that. - And if that's the case,
你和你的家人会得到妥善安置
you and your family will be taken care of.
他们已经给我提供认罪条件了
They're already offering me a plea.
你还没被起诉呢
You haven't even been charged yet.
如果我合作的话
If I cooperate.
你能少坐几年牢
You'll do less time,
但你的家人会一无所有
but your family will have nothing.
等你出来他们还是一无所有
They'll still have nothing when you get out.
你作证指认雷蒙德
You testify against Raymond,
他也不会有事  因为他们只有你的证词作证据
and he'll still walk because all they'll have is your word.
而现在你的证词没多少可信度
And that doesn't count for much right now.
他要是不害怕你就不会来了
You wouldn't be here if he wasn't afraid.
我来不是因为他害怕了
I'm not here because he's afraid.
是因为你害怕了
I'm here because you are.
我要确定你不会做蠢事
And I want to make sure you don't do anything stupid.
在反复和北京沟通后
After repeated conversations with Beijing
他们坚持他们的立场
they remain intractable in their position.
我今早命令一个航母战斗群
This morning I gave orders for a carrier group
在冲绳海域重新部署
to reposition near Okinawa.
这样我们的舰只不会直接
This won't put our ships in direct confrontation
和中国军舰对峙
with the Chinese vessels,
但又能把对方纳入航母空袭范围
but it will put them within reach of airstrikes.
我今天晚些时候会知会中国大使
I'll be informing the Chinese ambassador later today.
我们会和五角大楼联合发表声明
We'll release a statement in coordination with the Pentagon.
先生  我们的钐储量
Sir, our stockpiles of samarium
最多能再坚持两个月
will only last another two months at most.
如果我们这么做
If we go this route --
我已经知道所有人的担忧
Yeah, I've -- I've heard everyone's concerns.
这是我的决定
And this is the decision I've made.
有问题吗
Any questions?
好的  谢谢
Okay. Thank you.
弗兰克
Frank.
进行的怎么样
How'd it go?
我们有些问题需要后续澄清
We have a few follow-up questions that we have to address.
比如什么
Like what?
没什么要紧的
Oh, nothing major.
就是零七碎八  一点细节
Just odds and ends. A few details.
我以为这调查会简短而温和
I was under the impression this would be short and sweet.
我也以为  但她不依不饶
So was I, but she's very deliberate.
这事得尽快平息  弗兰克
We need this over, Frank.
至少要尽快撇清跟白宫的关系
At least as far as the White House is concerned.
我们不能分心
We can't be distracted.
特别是局势如此紧张的时候
Not with warships on the move.
我确信马上就会结束了
I'm confident we're in the home stretch.
你看上去不像嘴上说得那么轻松
Well, you seem more concerned than you're letting on.
不  完全没有
Oh, no, not at all.
你在搓手
You're fidgeting.
是我的毕业戒指
It's my class ring.
我忘了我...
I forget I --
我把它埋了
I buried it.
什么
You what?
说来话长了
I -- it's a long story.
我从没见过你这么紧张  弗兰克
I've never seen you this stressed before, Frank.
我从没见过您这么疲惫  先生
Well, I've never seen you this tired before, sir.
您也有自己的圈
You've got rings of your own.
黑眼圈
Dark ones.
越发明显了  是吗
Yeah, they're getting worse, aren't they?
您该在总统办公室的沙发上多打打盹
You should take more naps on those sofas in the Oval.
如今光打盹可管不了用了  弗兰克
Oh, naps don't cut it these days, Frank.
一点都解不了乏
Not even a dent.
谎话连篇
Lie after lie.
先是对检察官  现在是对总统
First to a prosecutor, then to a president.
我觉得我全无防护
I feel exposed.
就像我手指上曾被戒指庇护的皮肤
Like the skin where my ring used to be.
强如阿喀琉斯  也终因踵上一箭毙命
Even Achilles was only as strong as his heel.
道格在哪  他老不接电话
Where's Doug? He's not answering his phone.
他去参加互助会了  先生
He went to a meeting, sir.
大白天的去干什么
In the middle of the day?
他现在可能在往回赶了
I think he's on his way back now.
我要他赶紧回来
I want him back now as soon as possible.
先生  这是给你的
Sir, this arrived for you.
是雷米跳槽去格兰顿-希尔时你送给他的手表
The watch you gave Remy when he left for Glendon Hill.
我从手表背面的名言认出来的
I recognized it from the quote on the back.
他留信息了吗
Was there a message?
没有  只有这块表
No. Just the watch.
赶紧联系道格
Let's find Doug.
好的  先生
Right away, sir.
希望你不介意塑料杯子
Forgive the plastic.
吕克·图伊曼斯  他有真本事
Luc Tuymans. He's the real thing.
那我就信你了
Well, I'll take your word.
这不是我的  这些全都不是
It's not mine. None of it.
在加州  你要是想卖房子
California, you want to sell your house,
你的房屋中介会先装修一番
your realtor decorates it.
起码会装个样板间
Well, one room at least.
你打算搬到哪去
Where you moving?
我在索诺玛有座小农场
Oh, I have a little ranch in Sonoma.
我妻子离开了
My wife's gone.
我的孩子也不和我说话
My kids won't talk to me.
至少我还有我的画
But at least I'll have my painting.
你还画画吗
You paint?
不画  农场也是胡扯
No. And there's no ranch.
但其余的话  其余的都是真的
But the rest of it -- the rest of it's true.
干杯
Cheers.
我是为杰奎琳·夏普而来
I'm here about Jacqueline Sharp.
我们在考虑雇用她
We're thinking of hiring her.
做说客吗
A lobbyist?
她可能赢不了连任竞选了
She could lose her re-elect.
现在局势对在位者不利
Not a great time to be an incumbent.
我知道你和她关系很近
I know you two are close.
你来是想要什么
So, you're looking for what?
推荐函吗
A recommendation?
我们是K街员工流动率最低的一家
We have the lowest turnover of any shop on K Street.
K街上有很多智囊公司  游说公司和倡导团体
这是有原因的
There's a reason.
格兰顿-希尔想用什么样的人
What are you looking for at Glendon Hill?
心狠手辣的人
A killer instinct.
那你找她算是找对人了
Well, she certainly has that.
恕我直言
Forgive me if I'm prying,
但是不是她造成了你的...
but did she have anything to do with your, uh...
出局
Departure?
杰姬做了她必须做的事
Jackie did what she had to do.
我永远不会原谅她
I'll never forgive her.
但我理解她为什么要这么做
But I understand why she did it.
她究竟做了什么
Did what exactly?
我用现金买的票
I paid cash for my ticket.
我非常谨慎
I was careful.
显然不够谨慎
Clearly not enough.
先生  赌场里到处是摄像头
Sir, the casino had cameras everywhere.
我根本无法避开
There was no way to avoid them.
但他们的监控录像肯定有几千小时
But there had to have been thousands of hours of footage.
他们怎么找出来的...
Now how they found that --
有个问题我必须要问  道格
I have to ask you a question, Doug.
我很抱歉  但你要如实作答
And I'm sorry, but I need you to be honest.
你是不是又开始酗酒了
Are you drinking again?
当然没有
God no.
真的吗
Truly?
想都没想过
It's not an option.
你最近的表现可很像喝醉了
Because it would explain a lot.
你完全有权生气
You have every right to be upset.
-这是我的错  -我已经顾不上生气了
- This was my fault. - I'm more concerned than I'm upset.
我现在需要你  道格
I need you now, Doug.
非常需要
More than ever.
我明白
I know.
你我都不年轻了
We're not young men.
一旦失败  都会老死在牢里
If we fail, we'll die in a cage.
我最近不在状态
I haven't been myself lately.
你14年前也是这么说的
That's what you said to me 14 years ago.
我给了你第二次机会  也收获了回报
When I gave you a second chance, it paid off.
你戒酒了  道格
You got clean, Doug.
这份工作是我最看重的  先生  无比重要
Nothing means more to me than this job, sir. Nothing.
无论发生了什么
Whatever's going on,
我要知道你能搞定
I need to know that it can be managed.
如果你需要我的帮助
And if you need my help,
我会伸出援手
I'm here to help you.
我没事  先生
I'm good, sir.
我能解决好  局面会好转的
I can handle myself. Things'll be different.
我从没给过别人第三次机会
I've never given someone a third chance.
但现在我再给你一次机会
Until this very moment.
我非常感激
And I'm grateful.
我不会让你后悔的
You won't regret it.
请相信这一点  先生
Please believe that, sir.
是雷米让他们找到录像的
It was Remy who alerted them to the footage.
这是他的离职礼物
His going-away gift.
读读背面
Read the back.
你觉得他想传达什么信息
What do you think he's trying to say?
我不知道  找到他  给我安排一次会面
I don't know, but track him down and set up a meeting.
邓巴那边怎么办
What about Dunbar?
我们没法逃开事实
We can't run from the facts.
你让我说什么  我就说什么
I'll say whatever you want me to say.
我负全责
I'll take responsibility for all of it.
她可能会起诉你
She could indict you.
幕僚就是做这个的
That's what having a staff is for.
我有个更好的解决办法
I have a better solution.
-我们一起承担责任  -怎么做
- We'll both take responsibility. - How?
后天和邓巴安排一次会面
Set up an interview with Dunbar. Day after tomorrow.
-我们俩需要时间做足准备  -是  先生
- You and I need time to do our homework. - Yes, sir.
这是什么时候弄的
When did this happen?
密查姆帮我修好了
Meechum helped me fix it.
如果他们不让我跑步  我总得想办法健身
If they're not gonna let me run, I have to work out some way.
你把它搬上楼了
You carried it all the way up here?
更隐秘  有人帮我
For privacy. I had help.
-密查姆  -没错
- Meechum. - That's right.
他还真是样样通
Well, he's a jack of all trades.
-工匠  搬家具的  -肉盾
- Handyman. Furniture mover. - Human shield.
有多糟
How bad is it?
很糟
Bad.
他们有证据证明道格出现在不该出现的地方
They have evidence of Doug being where he shouldn't have been.
你打算怎么办
What are you gonna do?
讲实话
Tell the truth.
-你该不会真打算...  -不是全部
- You're not actually gonna -- - Selectively.
别担心
Don't worry.
不过绊了一下  还没摔倒
It's a stumble, not a fall.
如果只是绊一下  你不会这个样子
You aren't like this when it's just a stumble.
-什么样子  -你害怕了  我看得出来
- Like how? - You're scared. I can tell.
1分39秒划五百米  这是我的最佳成绩
500 meters at 1:39. That was my best.
以此为目标吧
Shoot for that.
你怎么样
How have you been?
挺好
Okay.
-药挺有用的  -那就好
- The meds are helping. - Oh, that's good to hear.
坐吧
Let's have a seat.
街角那些人
Those people at the end of the street...
闹得挺厉害
it's intense.
他们一天到晚不消停  周末人数还翻番
They're there 24/7. Twice as many on the weekends.
我们现在都习惯了
We're so used to it by now.
我能脱鞋吗
Can I take off my shoes?
我觉得该穿得正式点  但我真不喜欢高跟鞋
I thought I should dress up, but I am not good with heels.
行  当然可以
Yes. Of course.
我妈妈说和裙子很搭
My mom said they went with the dress.
舒服多了
Much better.
梅根
Look, Megan,
我知道过去六个月很难熬
I know the last six months have been difficult,
但我需要你的帮助
but I need your help.
我们没能像预想的那样得到领导层的支持
We just don't have the support that we expected in the leadership.
我也猜到你不会只是想问问我的近况
Yeah, I figured this wasn't just about checking up on me.
你之前改过主意  我理解
You changed your mind before, and I understand why.
但现在你的情况似乎稳定多了
But now it seems as though things are more stable with you.
你愿意吗
Are you willing?
我都坐在你家了  说不有点过意不去
It's hard to say no when I'm in your house.
你也听到了外头那些人
Well, you hear those people out there.
他们声音很响  但我们要发出更高的声音
They're loud, but I think we need to be louder.
但这声音不能是我的
And it can't be my voice,
因为我已经是婴儿杀手  和出轨者
because I'm the baby killer, the cheater.
这声音得是你发出的
It needs to be your voice.
因为你没有污点
A clear voice.
我已经在军事法庭上作证了
I'm already testifying at the court martial.
但那里不对媒体开放
But that's closed to the media.
还不够
It's not enough.
这种事曾发生在很多人身上
There are so many people this has happened to.
为什么一定是我
Why does it have to be me?
因为是你打来了电话
Because you're the one who called.
你打算在麦金尼斯判刑之前发表吗
Are you gonna try to put it out before McGinnis gets sentenced?
赛斯  有空吗
Seth? You have a minute?
马特  我一会儿打给你
Matt, I have to call you back.
关门
Close the door.
副总统录用你的时候
When the vice president brought you on board,
我是反对的
I advised against it.
但我不得不承认你干得很好
But I can't deny you've done a good job.
谢谢你这么说
I appreciate you saying that.
我一直很注重保护副总统
I'm very protective of the vice president.
我很难跟旁人分担这份职责
I find it hard to share that duty with anyone else,
这也导致我可能出错
which leaves me open to error.
这是我的缺点之一
It's one of my faults.
正如我跟副总统说的那样
As I told the vice president,
我知道信任需要我自己争取
I understand that trust is something that I need to earn.
而且我得到工作的途径不正
And given how I got the job --
如果副总统信任你  那我就信任你
If the vice president trusts you, then I trust you.
我们现在是一个团队
We're a team now.
而且我也没法孤军奋战
And the truth is I can't do this alone.
要我做任何事都行
Anything and everything you ask of me.
可能与媒体无关
It might have nothing to do with the media.
新闻发言人不过是个名号
Press Secretary is just a title.
很好
Good.
我们有两个任务
We have two tasks.
首先  找到雷米·丹顿
First, find me Remy Danton.
但要小心
But be discreet.
我去找他
I'll track him down.
其次  我要你翻阅副总统的行程记录
Second, I need you to go through the Vice President's travel logs.
过去十年的所有记录
Everything in the past 10 years.
我们要找什么
What are we looking for?
任何软肋
Anything that could hurt us.
我从前往后找
I'll work forward.
你从后往前
You work backward.
马上去办  还有道格
I'm on it. And Doug?
谢谢
Thanks.
南茜  帮我订部新手机
Nancy, I need you to order me a new phone.
你说是"零七碎八""马上就会结束"
You said "Odds and ends." The "Home stretch."
我几个小时前才看到了这些内容
I was presented with this information just hours ago.
这是能招致弹劾的罪行  弗兰克
We're talking about impeachable offenses, Frank.
完全不会  先生
Not at all, sir.
你的幕僚长...
Your Chief of Staff was --
我当时觉得赌场跟这事有关
I had a gut feeling that the casino was involved.
我派道格去查了
I sent Doug down there to get to the bottom of it.
你一发现联系就该马上去找司法部
You should have taken this to the DOJ the first inkling you had --
我当时就不想那么做
That's exactly what I didn't want.
万一没有什么  我却制造事端
To create some ruckus if nothing was going on?
你不能私自调查  弗兰克
You can't go on conducting your own investigations, Frank.
查明真相  尽职调查  随您怎么说
Fact-finding, due diligence, whatever you want to call it.
如果有任何违法行为  我必须知道
If any laws were being broken, I wanted to know.
你就要这么跟邓巴说吗
And that's what you want to tell Dunbar.
我不想透露我们的外交手段
That I didn't want to disclose our diplomatic protocols.
我担心中期选举
That I was concerned about the midterms.
我还想保护美国总统
And that I wanted to protect the President of the United States.
或许我做得不对
Now, maybe what I did was wrong,
但我没干任何违法的事
but I didn't do anything illegal.
你确定
You certain of that?
我跟我的律师认真探讨过了
I've discussed this at length with my lawyers.
即使我们承认这一切
Dunbar does not strike me as the sort of person
我觉得邓巴也不会就此打住
who will put on the brakes, even if we admit all of this.
反而还可能促使她继续深挖
In fact, it might encourage her to dig deeper.
说得对
You're right.
所以我打算上交我全部的行程记录
Which is why I want to hand over all of my travel logs.
我觉得您也该这么做
And I think you should, too.
自愿上交吗
Volunteer them?
是的  表示我们乐意合作
Yeah. As a gesture of cooperation.
我们表示做得够多了
Haven't we made enough gestures?
这样她就不会那么叫劲了
That'll take the wind outta her sails.
不  我不想让她
No. I don't, uh, want her,
仔细查看我所有的行踪
uh, poring over every one of my comings and goings.
他是在担心他的婚姻咨询
He's worried about his marriage counseling,
他也该担心
as he should be.
如果您是在担心您的婚姻咨询
If you're worried about your marriage counseling,
您不必担心
you shouldn't be.
如果被外界知道  会造成多大影响
Imagine the fallout if the public were to find out that --
那是大海里的一根针
A needle in a haystack,
还不是邓巴要找的那根
and not a needle that Dunbar is looking for.
她已经会见了一半的国会议员
She's interviewed half of Congress.
这女人是要见血
That woman's after blood.
而不是八卦
But not for gossip.
就算她真的起疑了
And even if she does raise an eyebrow,
您只是去探望一位生病的朋友  不是吗
you were visiting a sick friend, weren't you?
是的  表面上是这样
Yeah, ostensibly.
这她没什么可说的
Well, she couldn't possibly find any fault with that.
叫嘉利克过来
I'd like Galich in here.
那我就不打扰了
I'll let you two talk privately.
你什么时候去见邓巴
When are you seeing Dunbar?
明天  这样您也有时间准备
Tomorrow, so you have some time.
我会跟比尔谈谈  回头找你
Well, I'll speak to Bill and get back to you.
他会建议您不要这么做  这是他职责所在
He'll advise you against it, which is his job.
但我会强烈建议您想想政治而不是法律
But I would just encourage you to think politics and not legalese.
谢谢  先生
Thank you, sir.
议员女士
Congresswoman?
我为什么要投票给你
Why should I vote for you?
没事  马克
It's -- it's okay, Mark.
晚安
Goodnight.
你看起来很疲惫
You look tired.
忙了一天竞选吗
Long day on the campaign trail?
你在这干什么
What are you doing here?
你没跟我说过哈维梅耶女儿的事
You never told me about Havemeyer's daughter.
大家都知道
Everyone knows that.
全世界都知道
The whole world knows.
但不知道你常去探望她
But not that you visited her.
而且是你泄露出去的
That you leaked it.
你大老远跑来加州就是为了问我这些
You came all the way to California to ask me about that?
我是到了加州才知道的
I came to California to find out about that.
我提出买下哈维梅耶的房子
I offered to buy Havemeyer's house,
但他就那么告诉我了
but he told me for nothing.
你说得对
You were right.
我确实忙了一天竞选
It has been a long day on the trail.
现在还不相上下
It's still a close race.
要是选民知道你是怎么当上党鞭就不会了
But not if the voters know how you became whip.
你这是在威胁我吗
Are you honestly threatening me?
安排和弗兰克的会面
Set up a meeting with Frank.
我不在乎你怎么说
I don't care what you talk about,
只要是你单独一人  会面也有记录就行
long as you're alone and the meeting is on the books.
然后你去和邓巴谈
Then you're gonna sit down with Dunbar.
她已经问完我了
I've already done my interview.
告诉她  是弗兰克逼你那么说的
Tell her Frank grilled you on your testimony.
作伪证吗
Perjure myself?
保住你的位子
Save your seat.
你说出去吧
You know what? Tell everyone.
想想那会有什么后果
Think how that'd play out.
我不在乎
I don't care.
你真要为了弗兰克毁了自己吗
You'd really toss yourself off a cliff for Frank?
我不效忠于弗兰克·安德伍德
I have zero allegiance for Frank Underwood.
我不会受他操纵
I won't be manipulated by him.
我更不会被你操纵
And I sure as fuck won't be manipulated by you.
我不是虚张声势
I'm not bluffing.
那我就是对的
Then I was right.
关于什么
About what?
你根本不在乎我
How little I meant.
那跟这个没关系
That has nothing to do with this.
当然有关系
It has everything to do with this.
我应该觉得恶心  但我没有
I should feel disgusted, but I don't.
只是特别失望
Just supremely disappointed.
我们十分钟前接到电话
We got the call 10 minutes ago.
直接从白宫顾问那里打来的
Direct from the White House counsel.
总统要上交一切吗
The President's turning over everything?
从他就职那天开始
From the day he took office.
肯定会包括他去拜访那位朋友吗
And we're sure this includes the visits to his friend?
当然  安保人员全部出动
It has to. It was full security detail.
老天啊
Phenomenal.
我们有下手的地方了
We have something we can work with.
关于我的记录...
Now, as for my logs...
没有问题
They're clean.
你拿生命打包票吗
You'd bet your life on that?
是的
I would.
我也是  先生
Me, too, sir.
我们已经检查了两次  反复检查
We've been through 'em twice, backward and forward.
我的声明呢
My statement?
在你的收件箱里
In your inbox.
我看过了  塞斯干得很漂亮
I looked it over. Seth did a nice job.
会面一结束我们就要把消息发布出去
We need to go wide with this the moment the interview's over,
这样邓巴如果打算发布什么消息
so that we beat Dunbar to the punch
我们可以先发制人
in case she decides to release something.
我会守在电脑前
I'll be at my computer,
一收到道格的消息就按下"发送"键
ready to press "Send" the moment I hear from Doug.
你们俩睡过觉吗
Have either of you slept?
我们很清醒  全速运转
We're awake. Fully operational.
你去洗个澡  换件衣服
You take a shower and put on a fresh suit.
是  先生  我们在那边见
Yes, sir. I'll see you over there.
你有至少三小时
You have at least three hours.
打个盹吧  去我办公室睡
Take a nap. You can use my office.
你作证的时候麦金尼斯将军就在法庭里
General McGinnis was in the courtroom when you testified.
是的
Yes.
你私下见过他吗
Had you seen him in person --
在他侵犯你之后
I mean, since he assaulted you?
没有
No.
那是什么感觉
So what was that like?
不愉快
Not fun.
怎么个不愉快
Not fun how?
很难受  真的很难受
It was hard. Really hard.
听着  梅根
Look, Megan,
我同意把文章的焦点转移到你身上
I -- I agreed to change the focus of my piece to focus on you,
我也知道这肯定很难
and, you know, I know this has gotta be hard.
但你得帮帮我
I need you to help me out a little bit.
很抱歉
I'm sorry.
我不是很擅长这个  我很紧张
I'm not very good at this. I'm nervous.
你打电话去安德伍德夫人的访谈时挺好的
You seemed fine when you called into Mrs. Underwood's interview.
她在电话那头跟我在一起
She was there with me on the phone.
你的紧张情绪
Your nerves.
我知道自你被侵犯后  这一直是个问题
I know that's been an issue since the assault.
那种防御心理
The defense brought up
引起了情绪与精神的不稳定
what they called emotional and mental instability.
总是那样
That's what always happens.
被攻击的人会再次被攻击
The person who was attacked gets attacked all over again.
你有什么感觉
How did that make you feel?
让我觉得愤怒
It made me angry.
律师一直问我恐慌症的事
The lawyer kept coming after me about my panic attacks,
和我的抗抑郁药
my antidepressants.
但我只是紧紧盯着麦金尼斯
But I just kept staring at McGinnis.
我想让他知道我能承受
I wanted him to see I could take it.
我很坚强
That I was strong.
我想让他先转过脸去
I wanted to make him look away first.
他有吗
And did he?
是的  当我说到他不只是侵犯了我的身体
Yes. When I said he did more than violate my body.
还背叛了自己的国家
He betrayed his country.
毁了海军陆战队的声誉
He robbed it of a good Marine.
我们谈谈国会正在谈论的
Let's talk about the Sexual Assault Bill
性侵法案吧
that's in front of Congress right now.
有人提出了很强烈的反对意见
You know it's taken some significant opposition,
尤其是另一个老兵
most notably from another veteran,
杰奎琳·夏普
Jacqueline Sharp.
要我说  她也背叛了自己的国家
If you ask me, she's betraying her country, too.
邓巴女士
Ms. Dunbar.
副总统先生
Mr. Vice President.
谢谢你多给我们几天时间
Thank you for giving us a few extra days.
耐心对我来说不是问题
I have no problem being patient,
只要能因此得到坦率的回答
as long as it leads to forthright answers.
我不会让你继续等待了
Well, I won't make you wait a moment longer.
可以开始了吗
Shall we?
你找到这里了
Oh, you found it.
请坐
Have a seat.
我们马上就完事了
We're just finishing up here.
你觉得怎么样  塔斯克先生
What do you think, Mr. Tusk?
留着还是剃了
Keep growing it or have it shaved?
还是留着吧
Ah, I guess I'll keep growing it.
没问题
Ah, no problem.
我把后面清理一下
Let me just clean up the back here.
不了  麦克  让我们单独待会儿
No, Mack, if you'd give me a couple of minutes.
谢了
Appreciate it.
大概十年前我在这里建造了这个地方
I had this place built down here about 10 years ago.
我厌倦了每两周都要开车穿过整个城市
I got tired of driving all the way across town every two weeks.
现在坐个电梯就到了
Now it's just an elevator ride.
真方便
Convenient.
你知道不方便的是什么吗
You know what isn't convenient?
在我办公室里挤下八个律师
Cramming eight attorneys into my office.
那里不是为召集我律所所有合伙人准备的
It was not designed for the entire partnership of my law firm.
他们比较担心拉尼根
They're worried about Lanagin.
他有点害怕  但他能挺住
He's a little shaky, but he'll hold up.
安德伍德
Underwood?
博奇出手了
Birch delivered.
邓巴提出斯坦普的问题了吧
And did Dunbar bring up Stamper?
会面是闭门的
The sessions are closed-door,
不过我想她肯定会提的
but I can't imagine she didn't.
那可怜的哈维梅耶那边呢
And what about poor Havemeyer?
他在杰姬·夏普的事上对我们有帮助吗
Was he any help to us on Jackie Sharp?
你的犹豫说明进展不顺吧
I do not take your hesitation as a promising sign.
我向来不喜欢让你失望
I never like disappointing you.
他什么都不知道吗
He had nothing.
不知道
No.
你觉得他是确实不知道呢
Now, do you think that's because there's nothing here,
还是他在保护她呢
or because he's protecting her.
他就是不知道
There's nothing there.
我可以再找一个别的议员
I can go to another congressman --
不行
No, no, no.
必须是个曝光率高的人
It has to be somebody high-profile,
领导层的人  才能引起轰动
someone in the leadership who will make waves.
那我再找找博奇
Let me get back to Birch.
太明显了
Too obvious,
既然他摆明了不会对弗兰克手软
now that he's shown no sympathy for Frank.
算盘不能打得太响
This can't look orchestrated.
多线作战  雷米
Multiple fronts, Remy.
必须得是杰姬·夏普
Has to be Jackie Sharp.
麦克
Mack?
把头发弄完吧
Let's finish up here.
我得回去干活儿了
I gotta get back to work.
没问题  老板
You got it, boss.
你也得去干活儿了
You need to get back to work, too.
我们说的事
And what we discussed?
把它们办成
Make it happen.
你之前否认你是去私下接触的人
You denied being a back channel.
我没否认
I did not deny.
我没有证实  因为这是机密信息
I chose not to confirm because it was classified.
但是你的办公室一直否认
But your office has consistently denied --
我让道格那么做的
I instructed Doug to do so,
还有我的新闻部
along with my communications department.
私下接触如果公之于众
When a back channel becomes public,
也就没什么用了
it defeats its purpose.
精心编造的谎言
An orchestrated deception --
如果我们不予置评
If we had refused to comment,
人们就会知道确有其事
it would have suggested that it was true,
就会危及这一渠道
which would have endangered the process.
我实在没办法
I really had no choice.
冯先生目前在迪拜
Mr. Feng is currently in Dubai.
我知道
I know.
他因腐败指控畏罪潜逃
He's fleeing corruption charges.
这不是他第一次被指控了
Not the first time he's been accused.
你的问题是什么呢
And your question?
我知道是他洗钱  副总统先生
I know he laundered the money, Mr. Vice President.
我找到确凿证据
It's just a matter of time
只是迟早的事
before I have the proof to substantiate that.
而我的问题就是  我再问一遍
So my question, which I am asking again,
你当时是否知情
is whether you knew.
那我就再回答一遍
And I will repeat my answer.
我当时并不知情
I did not.
我当时的确觉得有点不对劲
I did sense that something was awry,
道格知道我的担忧
and Doug was aware of my concerns.
我觉得调查清楚是我的责任
And I took it upon myself to find out.
副总统并不知情
The vice president didn't know.
你不知道他去赌场的事吗
You had no knowledge he was going to the casino?
不知道  但这并不代表
None. But that doesn't mean
我不对我手下的行为负责
I don't take full responsibility for my staff's behavior.
我责无旁贷
The buck stops with me.
那你发现了什么
And what did you find?
什么都没发现  没有非法行为
Nothing. No illegal activity.
我不像你那么神通广大
I don't have the same resources that you do.
如果你有所怀疑
If you suspected,
为什么不立即联络国家印第安人博彩委员会
why didn't you go immediately to the NIGC,
印第安人事务局  或者...
the BIA, the Department --
你得理解
You have to understand.
我们中期选举很吃力
We're facing very difficult midterms.
我不想为一些
I didn't want to bring attention
没有实据的判断而引发关注
to a series of allegations that may have no basis in fact.
或许这逻辑不是很合理
Now, that may have been misguided logic,
但这是我当时的选择
but that's how I chose to act.
错误全在我一个人头上
The mistake is mine and mine alone.
跟道格没关系
Not Doug's.
当然更算不到总统头上
And certainly not the president's.
我要是说我觉得
It shouldn't surprise you
我没看到事情的全部  你不会意外吧
if I say it feels like I am not getting the full picture.
所以我打算把全部展示给你
Which is why I'm prepared to give you the full picture.
奥利弗
Oliver?
白宫相信透明度
The White House believes in transparency.
副总统全部个人出行记录
All of the vice president's personal travel logs.
还包括我十年党鞭任期内的记录
And the last 10 years since I became whip.
和总统就职后的所有记录
As well as the president's since inauguration.
我们会面的对象和时间都没有任何问题
There should be no doubt as to whom we met with and when.
我很怀疑里面的内容
I am skeptical about what this contains.
这点我们也预料到了
Which is what we anticipated
所以奥利弗会全程在场
and why Oliver will walk you through anything
陪你审查全部材料
you might need to know.
全都在那儿了
It's all there.
但如果你还有其他疑问或要求
But if you have any questions or requests,
我们也愿意倾力协助
we'll be happy to facilitate.
刚开始我很紧张
I mean, at first I was really nervous.
但我一进入状态
But then as soon as I started getting into it,
开始吐露心声
starting speaking from my heart,
一切都自然脱口而出
all these things poured out.
那些我一度想说的
Everything I wanted to say.
我一直想说的都说出来了
That I've been wanting to say.
赛斯告诉我马特很满意
Seth told me that Matt was very impressed.
我还想做更多
I want to do more.
做更多采访
More interviews?
报刊采访  上电视
Articles. TV.
不论什么都可以
Whatever it takes.
我想帮忙
I want to help.
这很好  梅根
That's great, Megan.
谢谢你给我这个机会
Thank you for making me do this.
这对我来说是迈了一大步
It was a big step for me.
你还要赶飞机
You have a plane to catch.
如果你需要我做别的采访  我可以留下
I can stay longer, if you need me to do another.
不如你先回芝加哥
Why don't you head back to Chicago,
等我们制定好计划
and as soon as we put a plan together
再给你打电话
we can give you a buzz?
我能喝杯水吗
Can I get a glass of water?
自来水  还是瓶装的
Tap is fine, or you want bottled --
我自己来
I can get it.
汉纳希女士的车准备好了  夫人
We've got Ms. Hennessey's car ready, ma'am.
艾德华
Edward?
你去机场接她时
Did she seem all right
她看起来还好吗
when you picked her up from the airport?
您的意思是
How do you mean?
我不确定  正常吗
I don't know. Normal.
是的  可以这么说
Yes. I'd say so.
她情绪起伏很大
She's very up and down.
反复无常  容易激动
Very skittish and manic.
她确实有点紧张
I guess she did seem nervous.
我们没怎么交流
We didn't talk much.
我去看看她
I'll get her.
我在外面等
I'll be outside.
梅根
Megan?
我自己来
I've got it.
真的
Really.
我没事
I'm okay.
车在外面等着了
The car is ready whenever you are.
谢谢你
Thank you for everything.
一路顺风  保持联系
Have a safe flight. I'll be in touch.
我与邓巴女士的谈话卓有成效
I just had a very productive interview with Ms. Dunbar.
发新闻稿
Send out the press release.
非常感谢
Thank you very much.
您还好吗  夫人
You okay, ma'am?
我没事  我只是打碎了
Oh, I'm fine. I just dropped...
请让我来
Please, let me.
没关系  我可以的
Oh, uh, it's fine. I'm fine.
不  我来  您光着脚
No, I've got it. You're barefoot.
艾德华  真的  没事的
Edward, you don't have to. Really.
天啊  怎么了
Oh, no. What happened?
该死
Damn it.
我去找绷带
Let me get some bandages.
不用了
You don't have to.
我坚持  别动
No, I want to. Stay here.
目前的报导都是正面的
The coverage has been mostly positive so far.
邓巴那边呢
Dunbar's office?
他们只说很期待对记录的审核
All they've said is they look forward to reviewing the logs.
有人提到道格吗
Any heat on Doug?
有一些
Some.
很多人要求我发表评论
I'm getting a lot of requests for comments.
那是我的个人行动
I acted on my own.
我会全力配合司法部
And I will fully cooperate with the Justice Department.
可以这么对外说吗
We can put that out?
先生
Sir?
这或许会吸引更多注意
It might generate more interest.
注意我  而不是副总统
On me. Not the vice president.
无论什么情况我都能应付好
I can handle whatever comes my way.
就这么说
Put it out.
我去把最新的剪报都打出来  先生
I'll print you out the most recent clips, too, sir.
要想办法向邓巴透露风声吗
Should I find a way to tip off Dunbar?
还是顺其自然吧
Let nature take its course.
我们刚找到雷米
We got a hold of Remy.
他刚回来了
He just got back to town.
他在哪
Where is he?
我跟你的安保队都安排好了
I've arranged everything with your detail.
你做得很好  道格
You've done good work, Doug.
谢谢你  先生
Thank you, sir.
好了  这样好多了
There. That's much better.
谢谢  夫人
Thanks, ma'am.
我得走了
I'm gonna get going.
抱歉我有点喝醉了
I'm sorry I'm a little drunk.
这里是您家  您可以随心所欲
It's your house. You do whatever you want.
你也该喝一杯酒
You should have a glass of wine.
谢谢  夫人  但是...
I appreciate that, ma'am, but --
你已经下班了  对吗
You're off your shift, right?
是的  没错
I am. That's true.
那就不许说不喝
Then I won't take no for an answer.
您不该把好东西浪费在我身上
Uh, you shouldn't waste any of your good stuff on me.
我其实根本不懂品酒
I don't really know anything about wine.
那喝点波本威士忌怎么样
Then how about bourbon?
你肯定想喝一点
I bet you like a little of that.
我当然不介意能喝点波本威士忌
I definitely don't mind a bourbon from time to time.
那就喝波本威士忌
Then bourbon it is.
你现在很难找啊
You're a tough man to track down these days.
你拿到手表了
You got the watch.
变则善
"To improve is to change."
常变则至善
"To perfect is to change often."
那你想要什么样的变化呢
What sort of change are you looking for?
让我有选择余地的变化
Whichever leaves me options.
在格兰顿-希尔遇到麻烦了
Trouble at Glendon Hill?
带薪休假  直到调查结束
Paid leave till the investigation is over.
至少是带薪的
Well, at least you're being paid.
这是终止我合伙人身份的第一步
First step in terminating my partnership.
这种事你也懂
You know how things go.
无论发生什么
No matter what happens,
这都是我洗不掉的污点
there's a stain I can't wash out.
那么你在寻找就业机会喽
So you're looking for career opportunities.
我并不是要把自己整个卖给你
I'm not offering myself to you wholesale.
我会继续跟你斗  但是力度会小一点
I keep fighting you, but I can fight you less.
你说"小一点"的意思是...
And by "less" you mean...
让你痛  但不会让你完蛋
Enough to hurt, but not finish you.
作为回报  我在格兰顿-希尔之外也有前途
And in return I have a future beyond Glendon Hill,
不管是什么样的前途
whatever that might look like.
那么你是要保持中立
So you offer neutrality,
但最终会追随胜利者
but you'll go with the victor.
我想看着更厉害的人获胜
I figure let the best man win.
如果你失败了
And if you go down,
不会是因为我
it won't be because of me.
这已经挺够意思了
That's worth something.
你这是为什么
Where is this coming from?
保险  没别的
Insurance. That's all.
这跟杰姬有关吗
Does it have anything to do with Jackie?
已经结束了
That's over.
我知道你已经收服了博奇
I know you've got Birch in your pocket.
你不会选择乌麦克  我们太亲密了
Womack's not an option. We're too close.
但是杰奎琳
But Jacqueline...
这单纯是关于我的前途
This is about my future, pure and simple.
跟她没关系
She's not a part of it.
留着这块表吧  就当做诚意的象征
Keep the watch, as a token of good faith.
他虽然否认  但他在保护她
He might deny it, but he's protecting her.
他没有意识到的是
What he doesn't realize is
我比雷蒙德更不在乎杰姬
I have even less regard for Jackie than Raymond does.
可怜的雷米
Poor Remy.
感情用事
The heart can choke the mind
理智就会受到影响
when all its blood flows back unto itself.
他说"我不喜欢深色头发的女孩"
He said, "I don't like brunettes."
看来我差点错过了派对
Looks like I almost missed the party.
我已经下班了  先生
I'm off the clock, sir.
别紧张  弗兰西斯  我打破了一个杯子
Oh, relax. Francis, I broke a glass,
艾德华被一块碎片割伤了手
and Edward cut his hand on a piece of it.
天呐
Jesus.
我得给你换绷带了
I have to change that.
把那个解下来  我去拿新的...
Take that off, and I'll get fresh...
我希望您不要介意  先生
I hope you don't mind, sir.
我下了班...
I was off-duty --
她是不是...
Is she, uh...
喝醉了吗  有一点
Drunk? A little.
你喝了多少这东西
How many of these have you had?
喝了一点
A few.
不止一点吧
More than a few.
我可以用你的杯子吗
May I?
用吧
Please.
让我看看
Let me see.
没什么事
Oh, it's not too bad.
流了很多血
There's a lot of blood.
没有看上去那么糟
Looks worse than it is.
痛吗
Is it painful?
喝了酒不那么痛了
The bourbon helps.
如果痛你就说
Now you let me know if this hurts.
一点都不痛  先生
Not one bit, sir.
你头痛吗
How's your head?
没事
Fine.
睡前吃了几片阿司匹林
Took a few aspirin before I went to sleep.
你呢
You?
我睡得可香了
I slept like a baby.
很好  你需要好好睡一觉
Good. You needed that.
怎么了
What is it?
很奇怪
Something weird.
有个地址老是出现
This one address keeps popping up.
安德伍德吗
Underwood?
总统
The president.
早上好  密查姆
Morning, Meechum.
早上好  副总统先生
Morning, Mr. Vice President.
真是美好的一天
It's a beautiful day.
当美国政府爆出丑闻  需要进行彻底调查时
为了避免司法部的调查偏向现政府
国会会要求司法部任命特别检察官  进行全权独立的调查
特别检察官的人选必须是不担任政府公职的人员
美国历史上最著名的特别检察官
当属哈佛大学法学教授阿奇伯德·考克斯
1973年5月  考克斯被任命为负责调查水门事件的特别检察官
在调查过程中发现总统尼克松有违法嫌疑
尼克松遂命令司法部长解除考克斯的职务
但是当时连续两名司法部长都拒绝了总统的要求
并辞职抗议  考克斯最终还是被尼克松政府解职
但是他仍然被认为在水门事件中发挥了非常重要的影响
克林顿担任总统期间  在白水事件和莱温斯基丑闻爆发后
肯·斯塔尔被任命为特别检察官  调查克林顿一系列的丑闻
在他的努力下  国会启动了对克林顿的弹劾程序
但是最终因为没有获得足够票数  弹劾没有成功
斯塔尔在克林顿丑闻期间也成为全美知名的政治人物
美国法律规定  只有公民才能在政治活动或选举中进行捐赠
持有绿卡者也可以参加政治选举活动进行助选
但除此之外  外国公民  包括在美国持有合法签证者
都不能进行政治捐赠
最高法院对超级政治行动委员会做出裁定后
由于一些对超级政治行动委员会的捐款难以确定来源
一些政治组织也不对外公布捐助者的身份
所以在2012年美国总统大选中  很多媒体质疑
会不会有外国政治献金通过超级政治行动委员会
对特定候选人进行捐款  但是目前看  在大型的选举中
尚没有发现有确定的大额外国捐款者
本剧中的情节在现实中出现的可能性不大
2012年1月  美国最高法院在一项判决中
重新确认了不允许外国资金资助选举的禁令
翻译  章鱼X
翻译  冬麟
翻译  香茗小焙
翻译  某豚
翻译  艾瑞卡
翻译  卫老哥
翻译  痒痒
翻译  泽川
时间轴  chance-coco
后期  饿得慌
特效  宝宝
顾问  老杜
校对  草草
总监  草草
纸牌屋
第二季  第十一集
人人影视倾情奉献